# Myroslav Soroka

SENIOR FRONT-END ENGINEER WITH SHOPIFY EXPERIENCE

**Contact Details NATIONALITY:** Ukrainan **ADDRESS:** Kive, Ukraine

MAIL: myroslav.soroka130@gmail.com

### Professional Skills

HTML

CSS

**BOOTSTRAP** 

W3.CSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

HTML DOM

**XML** 

**ANGULAR** 

**BACKBONE.JS** 

EMBER.JS

**REACT** 

SHOPIFY PLUS

SHOPIFY THEME

SHOPIFY TEMPLATE

SHOPIFY APP

## English

# Education

Master degree, Kyiv Polytechnic Institute, Kiev

## **ABOUT ME**

Senior Front-end engineer with over 5 years of successful experience in software development with Shopify experience.

Understand and master latest technology in a short time.

Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

Always set high goals and devotes all effort and enthusiasm to achieve them

# **Project Experience**

#### Front-end developer (2015 - 2017)

- Converted multiple website designs using REACT/HTML/CSS/Bootstrap from figma&psd designs.
- Under close connection with the Back-end team, the design for various types of projects was perfectly completed and greatly contributed to the success of the business.

#### Senior Front-end developer / CTO role(2017- present)

- Independently responsible for front-end development of project for large-scale work and served as CTO at the invitation of several companies, greatly contributing to the achievement of the company's goals.
- Ability to handle various tasks skillfully, performed the role of a project manager with accurate logic for small and medium-sized businesses, and solved various problems raised in corporate activities.

### Shopify developer(2018- present)

- Converted Shopify store design from figma&pad design.
- Customized various Shopify theme&template.
- Developing various apps according to the needs of store managers and clients using CI/Laravel5.

# Interesting











Reading

Table tennis Football

Bicycle

**Swimming**